

## **Dominic Fung**

Bioinformatics and Statistics (BSc.)

Mississauga ON. Canada

#### Skills

Full stack development	5+ yrs.
Cloud computing/ Serverless technology	3+ yrs.
Web dev. & design	4+ yrs.
App (IOS/Android) development	2+ yrs.
Big data/ Data science	2+ yrs.
Distributed ledger technology	1+ yrs.

# Frameworks & Technologies

Typescript & Javascript	4+ yrs.
Reactjs & React-Native	4+ yrs.
AWS serverless	3+ yrs.
Python & Tensorflow	2+ yrs.
AWS Sagemaker	2+ yrs.
Java/ Kotlin/ Swift	1+ yrs.

## **Biography**

Dominic is from Mississauga, Ontario where he works as a full-stack developer at Romet Limited. Dom has 5 years of experience as a software developer with a focus on full-stack Javascript & Typescript app development hosted on AWS. He's also dabbled in AI and blockchain technologies using Tensorflow and smart contracts on NEO respectively. In his spare time, Dom plays acoustic renditions of 2000s punk-rock songs on his guitar and listens to Millennial Investing by The Investors's Podcast Network.

## Work Experience

#### Full-Stack Developer | Romet Limited

June 2021 - Today

Research & Development

Worked on Android and iOS native apps for gas meter field technician via Java/Swift with REST calls to AWS using API Gateway and lambda microservices. Maintained our cloud infrastructure using cloudformation and the serverless framework. Implemented multi-tiered deployment (test and production environments) with CI/CD features via CodeCommit, CodeBuild, CodePipeline and Code deploy. Augmented and implemented new features on the current dataportal built with Typescript React using GraphQL via AWS Amplify/Appsync talking to DynamoDB and RDS (Postgres). Worked on IoT Core and IoT Rules for data ingestion and device commission/decommission. Used React-Native to build prototype Android/iOS/Desktop apps to communicate directly with meters using serial communication (RS232).

#### Technical Specialist | BMO

May 2017 - June 2021

RPA. Data & AI - SmartCore

Helped deploy multiple Workfusion and UiPath (robotic process automation, RPA) platforms on premise and in private cloud. Wrote multiple reusable Java libraries (ie. DB connectors, SMTP/IMAP) shared across projects. Built a video streaming platform using Reactjs, Videojs and RTMP to monitor automation in real-time. Integrated authentication and security via Active Director & Cyberark.

#### IT Consultant | FDM Group

Jan 2017 - May 2019

Toronto, GTA

Focused on helping customers build Java applications using relational DB backends (PostgreSQL, MySQL). We utilized Spring Boot and the MVC design patterns.

## **Projects**

#### Oslyn.io | Your digital bandmate

Android & IOS App, Artificial intelligence Al



Oslyn is an app that listens to you play and accompanies you in real-time with a wide selection of pads, synths, and sounds.

As a data scientist, I used Tensorflow and AWS Sagemaker to train multiple model architectures (ie. Feed Forward, Recurrent Neural Net, etc.) utilizing 400+ labelled songs and pretraining on web scraped audio data.

As a developer, I used AWS Amplify & Cognito to authenticate and connect to our cloud infrastructure. DynamoDB & AWS Appsync (graphQL) to store and fetch user data. S3 to store audio and AI model binaries. I used React-Native + Java & Swift deployed on the Play Store and App Store for Android and IOS respectively.

% https://oslyn.io

### **Education**

2011 - 2016

Bioinformatics (BSc.) and Minor Statistics

University of Toronto Mississauga

#### **Interests**

- Playing Music
- Snowboarding
- All things Marvel

#### Contact

- 1406 Pickwick Dr. Mississauga ON. L5V 1V7
- $\Box$  +1 647 622 7764
- dominic.fung@icloud.com
- ★ http://dom-fung.com
- github.com/DominicFung

#### Nodis.io | Get Noticed

Webapp and Blockchain



Nodis' goal is to help small businesses around the world to get noticed by local communities. Nodis Challenge is our fun and interactive way to reach that goal. Nodis is a cryptocurrency, built on the NEO blockchain using Reactjs and MongoDB hosted on AWS EC2. I also helped test the smart contract on the NEO test network using Python.

- % https://nodis.io
- https://github.com/nodis-io

#### One Chanhs Co. | Bridal store

Serverless React store



Built with React and AWS Appsync. Stripe API for monetization. Used tailwind.css to allow my client greater design customizability.

- https://onechanhs.ca
- https://github.com/DominicFung/onechanhs

#### Logistical.ly

Desktop app via React-Electron



Windows desktop app built with Typescript, React and Electron to help a client find the lowest courier cost given a list of destinations and courier services.

https://github.com/DominicFung/logistical.ly

## **Certifications**



Amazon Web Services Solutions Architect Associate

Amazon Web Services (AWS) HDW98122JFRQQBGT



SAS Certified Advanced Programmer for SAS 9

SAS Institute AP019093v9



MTA: Database Fundamentals - Certified 2016

Microsoft 13090778